Guide to the News Service Biographical Files, circa 1930s - 2004
Duke University. University Archives
- Addition, 2004 [A2004-19] (Box 60)
  - Trustees (Box 114)
    - Rankin, Watson Smith [Duke Endowment Trustee], d. 9/8/1970 (Box 117)
    - Rauch, Henry E. (Box 117)
    - Reinhardt, Uwe E. (Box 117)
    - Reid, Elizabeth Brooks [Chairman, Institutional Advancement Committee], Trustee 1981-1993 (Box 117)
    - Reuben-Cooke, Wilhelmina M., Trustee 1989 (Box 117)
    - Reynolds, William Neal, d. 9/1951 (Box 117)
    - Rhyne, Charles S. (Box 117)
    - Richardson, Robert (Box 117)
    - Robertson, James David [Anatomy], d. 8/11/1995 (Box 117)
    - Robertson, Reuben B., d. 3/13/1960 (Box 117)
    - Robinson, Frederick (Rick) [Student Trustee], 1 July 1978 - 30 June 1981 (Box 117)
    - Robinson, Roscoe R. "Ike" (Box 117)
    - Robinson, Sally Dalton, Trustee 1995-1999 (Box 117)
    - Robinson, W. S. O'B (Box 117)
    - Roper, Daniel Calhoun, 15797 (Box 117)
    - Rowlett, Margaret (Box 117)
    - Ruark, Henry Gibbons (Box 117)
    - Sample, Paul Lindsay, d. 12/8/1953 (Box 117)
    - Sands, Alexander Hamilton [and Director of Duke Power; Duke Endowment Trustee], d. 4/1960 (Box 117)
    - Schwarz, John A., Trustee to 2001 (Box 117)
    - Sears, Amy, Trustee 1988- (Box 117)
    - Semans, Mary Trent [see also Dr. James H. Semans] (Box 117)
    - Separk, Joseph Henry, d. 4/1950 (Box 118)
    - Sherrill, Frank O. (Box 118)
    - Sherrill, John Bascom, d. 2/28/1934 (Box 118)
    - Sidbury, J. Buren, d. 1/7/1968 (Box 118)
    - Sidman, Edwin (Box 118)
    - Simmons, Furnifold McLendel, d. 5/1/1940 (Box 118)
    - Simpson, Dorothy Lewis, Trustee 1988- (Box 118)
    - Smith, Charles M., Trustee to 2001 (Box 118)
    - Smith, Herbert (Box 118)
    - Smith, James Raymond, d. 2/1987 (Box 118)
    - Smith, Lanty (Box 118)
    - Smith, Willis (Box 118)
    - Southgate, Thomas F., Jr. (Box 118)
    - Spears, Mrs. Marshall T. (Box 118)
    - Stanbury, Walter Albert (Box 118)
    - Stern, Kay Goodman (Mrs. Sidney J.), Trustee 1988- (Box 118)
    - Stockton, Thomas B. (Box 118)
    - Tannenbaum, Abraham Jack (Box 118)
    - Temple, Arthur (Box 118)
    - Thomas, David, Trustee 1988- (Box 118)
    - Thomas, James Augustus, d. 9/10/1940 (Box 118)
    - Tift, Susan Elizabeth (Box 118)
    - Timberlake, Susan A., 1996-1999 (Box 118)
    - Tisdale, Wright, d. 9/3/1975 (Box 118)
    - Tobias, Randall L., Trustee 1988 (Box 118)
    - Toms, Clinton White, d. 8/29/1936 (Box 118)
    - Tosteson, Daniel Charles, 1987-1993 (Box 118)
    - Towe, Kenneth Crawford (Box 118)
    - Turner, Wilfred Dent [NC Lieutenant Gov.], d. 11/8/1933 (Box 118)
    - Turrentine, Samuel B. (Box 118)
    - Upchurch, Walter McGowan, Jr., d. 1/1989 (Box 118)
    - Upchurch, Williamm Merrimon, Jr. (Box 118)
    - Vess, Tomalei J. (Box 118)
    - Vincent, Jim (Box 118)
    - Von Canon, James Frederick (Box 118)
    - von der Heyden, Karl Mueller (Box 118)
    - Wade, Charles Byrd, Jr., d. 7/16/1994 (Box 118)
    - Wagoner, G. Richard, Jr. [also under Notables] (Box 118)
    - Wallace, Charles S. (Box 118)
    - Wallace, George Roberts (Box 118)
    - Watson, K. Brantley, d. 4/18/1976 (Box 118)
    - Way, Joseph Howell, d. 9/22/1927 (Box 118)
    - Weaver, Frank Miller (Box 118)
    - Webb, Earle W., d. 7/7/1965 (Box 118)
    - Weeks, Kenneth Durham (Box 118)
    - Wester, Thaddeus B. (Box 118)
    - Westmoreland, Timothy M. [Student Trustee] (Box 118)
    - Whitehead, Edwin C. (Box 118)
    - Williams, A. Morris, Jr., Trustee 1989- (Box 118)
    - Williams, Neil, Jr. (Box 118)
    - Williams, Rusty (Box 118)
    - Wilson, Gary L. (Box 118)
    - Wilson, Mary Grace [Women's College] (Box 118)
    - Woodruff, Judy, Trustee 1988- (Box 118)
    - Wooten, John Council, d. 10/8/1936 (Box 118)
    - Yoh, Harold L., Jr. (Box 118)
    - Younger, Kenneth Glen, Trustee 1985-1991 (Box 118)
    - Terry Sanford (Box 119)
    - Terry Sanford (Box 120)
    - Terry Sanford (Box 121)
    - Terry Sanford (Box 122)